filebuzz.com 2019-05-22

# FileBuzz - Find Software Fast - Privacy Statement

FileBuzz is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy tells you about our online collection and use of data. Please take a few minutes to review this policy and feel free to contact us with any questions. Your continued use of the filebuzz.com site will constitute your acceptance of, and consent to, the terms of this policy.

 **Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**  
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.  
We do not collect any personal data from our visitors when they use our services.  
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

 **Log Files**  
When you visit this site, certain kinds of information, such as the website that referred you to us, your IP address, browser type and language, and access times, may be collected automatically as part of the site's operation. We also may collect navigational information, including information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions taken in connection with the site. These information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Use of Cookies and Other Technologies**  
FileBuzz does not uses "cookies".  However our ad service providers use cookies on our sites. We use the services of Google Adsense for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Google Adsense collects anonymous data typically through the use of cookies. To learn more about Google Adsense, including your ability to opt out of setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, go to http://www.google.com/privacy.html   We have no access to or control over these cookies. And they cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. However you have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. 

**Links to External Sites  
**We link to websites, including software authors websites. They have different privacy policies and practices from those disclosed here. We assume no responsibility for the policies or practices of such linked sites, and encourage you to become acquainted with them prior to use.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. We will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes here or on our home pagel. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit one of our sites.

**Contact Information**  
For additional information, please contact us using contact link at site footer.
